A Guide to the Fairfax County Road Petitions, 1844-1908
Fairfax Circuit Court Historic Records Center
- Thompson, B. J. November, 1902 (Box-folder 9: RP-329)
  Road leading from Sideburn Station to the new cut road where it intersects with Old Braddock Road
- Berry, Joseph November, 1903 (Box-folder 9: RP-330)
  Road across the bed of a lake or pond in the Town of Wiehle
- Hunter, R. W. May, 1903 (Box-folder 9: RP-331)
  Road from section of Ball's Hill...following the general course of the old Army Road and intersecting with Langley - Lewinsville Road
- Hurst, Mordecai April, 1903 (Box-folder 10: RP-332)
  Road from Mount Vernon Road between the City of Alexandria and Mount Vernon to Telegraph Road
- Kincheloe, W. S. January, 1903 (Box-folder 10: RP-333)
  Road leading from Yates Ford Road to a point near Lewis Woodyards
- Mason, J. P. H. May, 1903 (Box-folder 10: RP-334)
  Road from Accotink Station to Accotink Village to a point on the northwest side of Telegraph Road at or near the corner of the lands of Nevitt and Higham
- Saunders, J. F. August, 1903 (Box-folder 10: RP-335)
  Road from point on Sawyers Road to Hunter's Mill Crossing on the S. R. Way
- Southern Railway Company September, 1903 (Box-folder 10: RP-336)
  Change: road and overhead bridge at Fairfax Station
- Talbott, John T. March, 1903 (Box-folder 10: RP-337)
  Road from a point on the Rolling Road at the corner between Young and Javin's farms to the Braddock Road
- Washington Southern Railway Co. September, 1903 (Box-folder 10: RP-338)
  Change: Road at Pohick Station
- Southern Railway Company September, 1904 (Box-folder 10: RP-339)
  Change: Public Road at Herbert's Crossing
- Southern Railway Company May, 1904 (Box-folder 10: RP-340)
  Change/Establish road at Southern Railway Crossing at Burke's Station
- Staats, Peter V. January, 1904 (Box-folder 10: RP-341)
  Change: Road leading from Hunter's Mill to Freedom Hill
- Washington Southern Railway Co. January, 1904 (Box-folder 10: RP-342)
  Change/Establish: Road at Accotink Station in the Mount Vernon District
- Washington Southern Railway Co. January, 1904 (Box-folder 10: RP-343)
  Change: Road near Lorton through lands of John Plaskett
- Woodyard, R. W. September, 1904 (Box-folder 10: RP-344)
  Road from Fords Mill Road to the Yates Ford Road
- Great Falls & Old Dominion November, 1905 (Box-folder 10: RP-345)
  Change: Country Road through lands of Charles Cutts
- Pickett, R. L. September, 1905 (Box-folder 10: RP-346)
  Change:'Talbert' Road to line between Martin and Kilbourn to the Railroad Station
- Walters, U. S. December, 1905 (Box-folder 10: RP-347)
  Road from Georgetown and Leesburg Turnpike to Great Falls on the Potomac River
- Riverside Farm September, 1906 (Box-folder 10: RP-348)
  Repair River Road near Riverside and Hunter's in Alexandria
- Sanders, C. S. November, 1906 (Box-folder 10: RP-349)
  Road from Brown's Mill...to a point on Hunter Mill Road
- Terrett, J. W. May, 1906 (Box-folder 10: RP-350)
  Road across Creed's land to Bailey's Crossroads to Theological Seminary Road
- Washington Southern Railway Co. June, 1906 (Box-folder 10: RP-351)
  Change: Little River Turnpike bridge near Alexandria; over the stream on the road running from Little River Turnpike over Annandale to Falls Church, in the Falls Church District
- Wells, E. W. September, 1906 (Box-folder 10: RP-352)
  Change: County Road from the Warrenton Pike to Pleasant Valley
- Byrne, Henry M. May, 1907 (Box-folder 10: RP-353)
  Discontinue road running from Fairfax Falls Church Road near Merrifield to Little River Turnpike near Davis' Store & Horace Gibson's shop
- Elgin, D. B. May, 1907 (Box-folder 10: RP-354)
  Discontinue county road from Little River Turnpike to point on Fairfax- Falls Church Road
- Whitesell, S. S. March, 1907 (Box-folder 10: RP-355)
  Road from Oakton, VA running west to a point on Vale Road near Montgomery
- Wrenn, Sidney March, 1907 (Box-folder 10: RP-356)
  Road starting from the corner of Robert Wrenn on the Centreville and Chantilly Road...to the Braddock Road
- Donovan, J. E. January, 1908 (Box-folder 10: RP-357)
  Road from site of old Fairfax Station to the new Fairfax Station (Lee District)
- Brown, Joseph Unknown (Box-folder 10: RP-358)
  Occoquan Road